快 快
Move, move, move.
告诉我为什么我们看这个 而不是看电影?
Tell me again why we chose this over seeing the movie.
如果车手哪怕有一毫秒的注意力不集中
If these guys lose focus for even a millisecond...
你就要用铲子把他们从围栏上铲去 用铲子
you have to scrape them off the fence with a shovel.
你是来看出车祸的?
You come hoping to see a crash?
不 我是来看他们比赛
No, I would like to see them complete...
当然也是看车祸的
Of course it's to see a crash.
- 你真变态 亨特 - 加油
- You're sick, Hunt. - Come on!
看 尼克带着我们的东西来了
Look, here comes Nick with our stuff.
- 嘿 老兄 - 他来了
- Hey, bud. - There he is.
好
Yes.
- 嗨 宝贝 - 嗨
- Hi, babe. - Hey.
天啊
Oh, my God. Ha, ha.
该少吃点快餐了 尼克
Uh, time to lay off the Funyuns, Nicky boy.
谢谢 哥们
Oh, thanks, buddy.
- 喔 太好了 - 耶 好呀
- Ah, great. - Yeah! All right!
想喝点吗?
Oh. Here. Want a drink?
这是杰克吗?
Oh. Is that straight-up Jack?
是他喜欢的吉姆
It's his buddy Jim.
- 等会吧 - 嘿 伙计
- Maybe later, yeah? - Hey, sport.
我的女友能用用你的望远镜吗
Can my girl use your binoculars?
其实并不是望远镜 更应该说是…
Well, they're not really binoculars exactly. They're more...
想喝多少就喝多少吧
Drink as much as you like.
快 快
Go, go, go.
别冲动 伙计们
Whoa. Easy, fellas.
马克·赫尔弗雷奇想超车
Craig Perry shuts the door as...
克雷格·佩里挡住了他
Mark Helfrich tries to overtake him.
谢谢你让我放下学业 休息一下
Hey, thanks for making me take a study break.
我真的很需要
I really, really needed this.
借过 借过
Excuse me. Pardon me.
真是惊险
That was a close call..
糟糕 刚才发生了什么
Well, great. What did I just miss?
- 你能看见吗? - 我看不见
- Can you see, ma'am? - I'm sorry, not really.
你是否希望我坐到下面? 你介意吗
Would you like me to move down a bit? Would you mind?
我很乐意
Be glad to. Thanks, man.
- 谢谢 - 没想到还有这么有风度的人
- Thank you.- And I thought chivalry was dead.
不是的 我的牛仔就是这样的人
Heh. That's not true. I have my cowboy right here.
换个地方亲热吧
Get a room, guys.
嘿 塞上这个
Hey. Put these in.
- 喔 妈妈 不要卫生棉 - 塞进去
- Oh, Mom, not tampons. - Put these...Put them in.
尼克 尼克
Nick. Nick.
- 这很痒 - 哦 妈妈
- This tickles. - Aw, Mom.
- 不 不 - 她把卫生棉塞进他们耳朵
- No, no, no. - She put tampons in their ears.
怎么能这样
That's just wrong, man.
我现在看不见了
I can't see now.
前面的坐下 混蛋
Hey, down in front, asshole.
接近半程了
Approaching the halfway point.
来了个邻居
There goes the neighborhood.
先生
Sir.
把你的脚拿开 谢谢
I need you to move your foot. Thank you.
这里建了多长时间了
Hey, how old is this place?
不知道
You got me.
快 快
Go, go, go.
准备轮胎
Tire up.
怎么了
What's that?
坐在这里安全吗
Is it safe to sit here?
当然 这里有围栏 我们没事
Of course. There's a fence there. We're fine.
别紧张
Relax.
下午3点在比赛重播频道
Replay of the Camping World Regional Series race...
重播世界冠军系列赛车
...is on the Replay Race Channel at 3p.m.
你感觉到了吗
Did you feel that?
刚才 就在这里
Just now, right here.
你没事吧
You okay?
我感觉有东西碰了我 奇怪的东西
Uh, I felt something touch me. Something strange.
对于有商业头脑的人来说…
For those of you with a business-minded head...
快 快
Go, go.
Come on, come on, come on.
- 两下就行 - 走 走
- Two's good. - Go, go, go.
不 等等 螺丝刀 糟糕
No, no, no, wait! The screwdriver! Shit!
噢
Oh.
快 快 快走
Come on, come on. Let's go, go, go!
快
Come on.
让开
Move!
快 离开这里
Go. Get the fuck out of here.
- 快 - 孩子们 等等
- Come on. - Boys, wait!
快 妈妈
Come on, Mom.
妈妈
Mom!
嘿 这里有个出口
Hey! Hey! There's an exit this way!
快 快
Come on, move.
- 亨特 - 珍妮特
- Hunt! - Janet!
走 快
Let's move. Come on.
那里有个出口 快
There's an exit over here. Come on.
快 这里来 快跑
Come on, come on! This way! Run!
- 劳丽 - 快
- Lori! - Move!
劳丽 快 离开这里
Lori. Lori, come on, let's go! Get out of here!
快 挤过去
Move! Push through!
快
Come on!
嘿 怎么了
Ow. Hey. What the hell?
你没事吧
Are you okay?
尼克 有什么事吗
Nick, is there something wrong?
天啊 这是杰克吗?
Oh, my God, is that straight-up Jack?
- 不 这是… - 他喜欢的吉姆
- No, no, it's his... - His buddy Jim.
你进过我的储藏室 你真阴险
You have been in my stash. You snake.
一个戴帽子的牛仔 他坐在这里
A cowboy in a hat. He sits here.
借过 借过
Excuse me. Pardon me.
噢
Oh, ha, ha.
牛仔
Cowboy.
卫生棉 她有卫生棉 塞在她孩子的耳朵里
Tampons. She gets tampons. She puts them in her kids' ears.
- 谁? - 她 就在那里
- Who? - Her, right there.
嘿 塞到耳朵里
Hey. Put these in your ears.
- 妈妈 不要卫生棉 - 塞到耳朵里
- Oh, Mom, not tampons. - Put them in your ear.
你怎么知道她会这么做?
Hey, how did you know she was gonna do that?
一个女人用这么多卫生棉
That's a lot of tampons for one woman.
尼克 尼克 怎么了
Nick? Nick. What's going on?
"坐下"什么的 "坐下…坐下…前面的坐下 混蛋"
"Down" something. "Down...Down in...Down in front, asshole."
前面的坐下 混蛋
Down in front, asshole.
来了个邻居
There goes the neighborhood.
先生 把你的脚拿开
Sir. I need you to move your foot.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 来吧 - 快
- Let's go. - Move it.
准备轮胎
Go. Pick up the tire.
这辆车要撞毁了
That's the car that's gonna crash.
我们要离开这里
We have to get out of here.
感谢上帝
Thank God.
- 什么? 不 我押了500美元 - 谁在乎…
- What? No, no. I got $500 on this race. - No one cares...
我们必须离开这里
We gotta get the fuck out of here.
我们会死 会发生车祸
We're gonna die. There's gonna be a crash.
小子 不要乱说
Hey, kid, that ain't funny.
- 我们现在就要走 - 放松点 尼克
- We gotta go right now. We gotta move. - Relax, Nick.
- 尼克 冷静 - 天啊
- Nick, calm down. - Oh, my God.
你什么毛病? 伙计? 滚开
What's your problem, bro? Get off of me, man.
- 快 我们走 - 等等 孩子们 等等
- Come on, let's go. - Wait. Boys, wait!
看我不揍扁你 你这娘们
I'm gonna kick your little ass, you pussy!
该死的
Goddamn it!
你这臭小子
God, you little punk.
- 安迪 - 呆在那儿别动
- Andy. - Stay there.
- 回来 小子 - 嘿 你这臭小子
- Come back here, kid! - Hey, you little prick!
- 你疯了吗 - 我都看见了
- Are you out of your mind? - I saw the whole thing.
- 会有重大车祸 - 当然会有车祸
- There's gonna be a crash. - Of course there's a crash.
赛车总会出车祸
There's always a fucking crash.
等等 什么车祸?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. What crash?
就是这个车祸 这就是我说的车祸
That fucking crash. That's what crash I'm talking about.
你开什么玩笑?
Are you shitting me?
我本来就是为了看这种场面才来的
That's the reason I come to these stupid redneck things.
不要见怪
No offense.
先生 不行
Sir. No, no, no...
我妻子还在里面 混蛋
But my wife's in there, asshole!
- 不 不行 - 放开我 我要去找她!
- No, you can't. - Let me go! I gotta find her!
- 哥们 冷静点 - 那可是我妻子
- Dude, relax. - That's my wife!
放开我 让我进去
Let me go! Get your hands off me!
你们都疯了吗?
Have you all lost your fucking mind?
《死神来了4》
- 来了 - 谢谢
- Here you go. - Thanks.
- 稍等一下 - 没关系
- Just a second. - That's okay.
尼克 你是做了一场梦 还是有声音告诉了你?
Nick, was it like a dream or like a voice in your head?
我看见了
I just...I just saw it.
我们能不能把它忘了?
Can we just try to forget about it?
你在开玩笑吗?
Are you kidding?
我永远不会忘了这一场景
I am never gonna get that image out of my head.
那女人的头就这么…
I mean, that girl's face just...
珍妮特 我知道很痛苦
Janet. Look, I know it's difficult.
我们都受到了惊吓 对吗?
We're all a little freaked out, okay?
可我们为什么还活着?
But why are we still alive?
谁在乎为什么
Who cares why? Okay?
我们活下来 是因为我们应该活下来
If we made it, we deserved it.
亨特 能不能不要摆弄你的幸运硬币了?
Hunt, will you give the lucky-coin shit a rest, please?
你们看
Guys, look.
(目前已经死亡52人)
(明晚将在麦肯利赛道举行追悼会)
我觉得我们应该参加追悼会
I think we should go to the memorial.
我不想去
I can't.
- 我不想去参加追悼会 - 对 算了吧
- I can't go back. - Yeah, screw that.
我们至少应该表示一下对这些人的尊重吧
We can pay our respects to those people.
什么人
What people?
那些没有这位…
People who didn't have a Dr. Xavier with...
先知让他们离开的人
them to tell them to get out of the way?
没有他在的那些人?
People who didn't have one of these?
来 珍妮特 吻它
Go ahead, Janet. Kiss it.
你可以选择正面还是反面 不过你知道我喜欢正面
It's your choice, heads or tails, but you know I like head.
真不敢相信我和你这种人一起出来
Can't believe I ever went out with you.
真不敢相信你这么幸运
Can't believe you were so lucky.
你们听我说 我们活了下来
Guys, look. We're here.
某种东西给了我们第二次机会
All right? Something gave us a second chance...
我们要心怀感恩 尽量利用这次机会
so let's be thankful and just try to make the most of it.
好吗
Okay?
我们走吧
Come on, let's go.
- 你没事吧 - 没事
- You okay? - Yeah.
好
Okay.
嗨
Hi.
嗨 我正盼着你来
Hi, I was hoping you'd come.
我想感谢你 你是个英雄
I wanted to thank you. You're a hero.
因为你的警告 我和两个儿子…
Because of your warning, we're alive...
都活了下来
and our two sons are safe.
听我说 我不是英雄 我没有…
Look, I'm not a hero, okay? I...I didn't...
你知道
You knew.
你怎么知道会出事?
How did you know it was gonna happen?
我也不肯定
I'm not sure.
我们很高兴你们都没事
Look, we're just glad you all are okay.
保重
Take care.
谢谢
Thank you.
很高兴你们没事
I'm glad you're safe.
谢谢
Thank you.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
我叫乔治 是个保安
I'm, uh, the security guard. George.
尼克
Nick.
劳丽
Lori.
- 你好 - 你好
- Hi. - Hi.
那里发生的事情很让我震惊
I was pretty freaked out about that back there.
我只想问你 你是怎么…
I just wanted to ask you how you...
你害死了我妻子
You killed my wife.
我本想进去找她 但是…
I wanted to go in there after her, but...
你
...you, uh...
很遗憾你失去了妻子
I'm sorry for your loss.
那么
Well...
没有人能永远活着 黑鬼
...nobody lives forever, nigger.
何必这么说话?
Hey, there's no need for that, man.
滚开 你这臭小子
Back off, you fucking freak.
你该离开了 先生
It's time for you to leave, sir.
时间?
Time?
你的时间也快到了 黑鬼
Your time's coming, chocolate.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
我刚做了个可怕的噩梦
I just had a really bad nightmare.
没事 只是个梦而已
It's okay, it's just a dream.
感觉很真实
It seemed real.
放松 继续睡觉
Just try to relax and go back to sleep.
我就在你身边
I'm right here.
狗娘养的!
Son of a bitch.
嘿 妈妈 这么晚了 你怎么还没睡
Hey, Ma. It's late. What are you doing up?
好
Okay.
不 一切都好 没事
No, no, no, everything's fine. Yeah, it's fine.
好
Okay.
时间到了
Time's up.
该死的
Goddamn it.
我要烧死你
I'll burn you.
她可能还没有…
She probably wasn't...
不 不 妈的
No, no, no! Fuck!
救命 救命 快醒醒!
Help me! Help! Wake up, please, anybody!
我着火了 烧着了
Please, I'm on fire! It's burning!
天啊
Oh, my God.
我屁股着火了 我屁股着火了
My ass is on fire! My ass is on fire!
我屁股着火了
My God! My ass is on fire!
嘿 宝贝 什么事?
Hey, babe, what's up?
劳丽 马上打开第7频道
Hey, Lori. Turn on Channel 7 right now.
还记得在赛车场见到的那个乡巴佬吗?
You remember that redneck from the racetrack?
- 他死了 - 什么?
- He's dead. - What?
好 等等
Yeah, hold on.
…这次罕见的事故
...from the freak accident.
调查仍然在进行中
Although the investigation is still on going...
医务人员宣布丹尼尔当场死亡
paramedics pronounced Daniels dead on the scene.
尼克 过来
Nick, get in here.
他是当地的步枪协会会员
A member of local PTA and NRA chapters...
是住在韦恩堡的一个非常低调的人
Carter Daniels lived quietly in Fort Wayne.
丹尼尔的死因还不清楚
Details are sketchy on how Daniels was killed.
目前只知道
All that is known at this time...
一辆拖吊车不知怎么
is that a tow truck dragged him...
把他在居民区的街道上拖了一段 然后发生了爆炸
down a residential street before the truck exploded.
想听些怪异的事情吗?
Wanna hear something freaky?
我以前见过这扇门
I've seen that door before.
晚间新闻将带来更多报道
More to come on our nightly news.
现在我们再来关注…
And now we'll checkin with our eye in the sky...
嘿 我要挂了 回头再联系
Hey, hey, I gotta go. I'll call you back.
好 再见
Okay, bye.
怎么了
What is it? What's wrong?
还记得我昨晚做了一个梦吗?
Remember that dream I had last night?
我觉得不是梦 就像是…
I...I don't think it was a dream. It was like...
就像是一个画面
It was like a vision.
有火焰 有个钩子
I mean, there were flames, and there was a hook...
还有那扇红色的门
and that red door.
现在那个有种族偏见的人死了
And now that racist guy is dead.
就像是我看见了他会怎么死的线索
It was like I saw clues as to how he was gonna die.
刚才我又看见了一个
Just now I saw another one.
等等 你看见了另一个人将会怎么死去?
Wait, wait, you saw how another person was gonna die?
- 是谁? - 我不知道
- Who was it? - I don't know.
根本没有解释 什么都没道理
It doesn't make any sense. Nothing makes any sense.
自从我离开赛车场 我就感觉
Ever since I left the racetrack, I feel like...
房间里有什么东西和我在一起
there's something in the room with me.
我是怎么了?
What is happening to me?
你今天来得很早啊
You're early today.
是啊 带的东西不多
Oh, yeah, light load.
来 过来
Hey, look. Come here.
我打赌你用石头肯定打不中那个告示牌
Bet you can't hit that sign with a rock.
好
Okay.
噢 好啊!
Oh, ha, ha, yeah.
好了 不要闹了
Okay, okay, knock it off.
- 好! - 嘿
- Yes! - Hey.
扔的好
Nice one.
你的孩子是傻了还是疯了?
Hey, what are you kids, stupid or something?
快滚
Get out of here.
好吧 过来 小伙子们
Okay, come here, guys. Um...
你们去玩电动吧 一小时后回来
I want you to go play video games. Come back in an hour.
- 好啊! - 玩好啊!
- All right! - You're welcome.
- 谢谢 - 谢谢妈妈
- Thanks. - Thanks, Mom.
- 我的"原子驱逐舰"玩得最好 - 不 我才是
- I'm first on "Atomic Destroyer." - No, I am.
嗨 夏安 对不起来晚了
Hi, Cheyenne, I'm sorry I'm late.
我5点钟和理查德有个预约
I had a 5:00 with Richard.
你没收到我们的电话留言吗?
Oh, you didn't get our message?
- 理查德今天出去了 - 什么?
- Richard's out today. - What?
他的街区有人死了
Someone got killed on his block.
全身着火 拖在街上走
Dragged down the street on fire.
- 多可怕啊 - 真不幸
- Isn't that terrible? - That's awful.
那么我的预约 有别人能接待吗
So my appointment? Is there someone else that can see me?
还有10分钟到6点 我们6点下班 所以…
Um, it's 10 to 6, and we close at 6, so...
我理解 可是孩子们的球赛结束的晚
I understand, but the soccer game ran late,
今晚又要和姐妹们出去玩
and it's girls' night out tonight...
我非常的期待 他们好几个月没在一起了
first time in months, and I'm so looking forward to this.
拜托 拜托了
Please. Please.
- 你看 - 真拿你没办法
- Look at this. - You're killing me.
谢谢 非常感谢
Thank you. Ah, thank you so much.
对不起 有点…
Excuse me, that's...
有一点点紧
That is a little...That's a little tight.
- 对不起 - 没关系
- Sorry. - That's okay.
迪迪 谢谢你为我加班了
So, Dee Dee, thank you for staying late.
你上次理发有多长时间了?
How long have you been cutting hair?
足够长了
Long enough.
该死的椅子
Goddamn chair.
对他们说过无数次该去修理了
I've only told them to fix it like a million times.
- 哦 迪迪 - 什么?
- Oh, Dee Dee? - Yeah?
能给我一杯水吗?
Could I please get some water?
- 没问题 - 谢谢
- No problem. - Thank you.
- 怎么样了? - 快好了
- How's it going? - Almost done.
我喜欢这种颜色 非常的甜蜜
I love the color. It's exactly honey.
是吗?
Do you think?
真对不起 对不起
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
不会再发生了
It won't happen again.
没关系
It's okay.
哇
Wow.
- 嘿 妈妈 - 嘿
- Hi, Mom. - Hey.
噢
Whoa.
天啊 你们没事吧!
Oh, my God, are you okay?
- 谢谢 迪迪 - 不客气
- Thanks, Dee Dee. - You're welcome.
希望你玩得愉快
Hope you have fun.
- 住手 - 你们别闹了!
- Stop. - Okay, guys, knock it off.
非常抱歉
I am so sorry about this.
我要一直盯着他们
These guys aren't gonna leave my sight...
直到他们上大学
until I ship them to college.
- 也许该上军校 - 对 也许
- Maybe military school? - Ha, yeah, maybe.
好了 孩子们 走吧
All right, boys, come on.
快走 上车
Let's go. Get in the car.
我看着你们呢
I've got my eye on you two.
哦 天呐!
Oh, my God!
是田径场上带小孩的那个女人
It's that lady with the kids, from the racetrack.
刚刚失去了一个
We just lost a really hot MILF.
- 伙计 这次是玩真的了 - 是啊
- Dude, this is serious. - Yeah.
你觉得尼克救了两个人都死
Don't you think it's weird...
是不是有点怪呢?
that two of the people Nick saved are dead?
把卫生棉塞进孩子耳朵里 这才叫怪呢
Weird is putting tampons in your kids' ears. That's weird.
她命该绝 只是早晚的问题
She was bound to die sooner or later.
所以我才叫你们过来
That's actually why we asked you guys to come over.
事故发生前
The night before it happened,
尼克做了一个非常奇怪的梦
Nick had a really strange dream.
太好了 我为此取消了我的高尔夫比赛
Great. I'm glad I cancelled my golf game for this. Good.
不过 那不是梦境
But it wasn't a dream.
就像是这些随机的声音和图像
It was like these random sounds and images.
虽然一点意思都没有
They really didn't make any sense.
不过我还是了解了导致他们死亡的原因 我还意识到…
And then I read what killed them and I realized that...
我能预感到下一个人如何死亡
I'd seen how the next person was gonna die.
等等 你说"下一个人"是什么意思?
Wait, what do you mean, "the next person"?
好吧 别笑 我们连夜上网查了一些预兆
Okay, don't laugh, but we stayed up Googling premonitions...
图像 标记类似的一些东西
visions, signs, things like that, just to see...
想看看我们到底能得到多少信息
how much information we could get.
有大量关于人们
There are tons of articles about people...
预感灾难的预兆的文章
who had a premonition about a disaster...
他们救了自己
they saved themselves...
然后却又死了
and then they died.
好吧 有人死了 那又怎么样?
Okay, so people died. So what?
所有活下的人都死了
Every survivor died.
按照他们当初应该在事故中死亡的顺序死掉
In the precise order they were meant to die in the accident.
那 我们活下来了啊
Well, we survived.
你意思是说 我们都得死?
So now does that mean we all die?
好吧 下一个是谁?
Well, who's next?
我不记得了
I don't remember.
或许有遗漏
But there might be an out.
有人说 顺序也可能被打乱
Some say the chain can be broken.
就像从死神手里救出某个人
Like if you were to intervene into someone else's death...
这一切就会结束了
that would end it.
不过还有的人说 除非顺序被完全破坏掉
But others say unless the chain is broken completely...
才能结束这场噩梦
then you're just changing the batting...
否则 你就是下一个
order, and sooner or later, you're up.
简直是一派胡言
That is some spooky psychobabble shit.
拜托了 闭嘴 这又不好笑
shut up, please. This is not funny.
他肯定看电视看多了
He could be watching a ton of TV.
你知道这对我意味着什么
You know what this does to me.
没事的 我们要做的就是
It's okay. All we're trying to do...
搞清楚到底发生了什么事
is figure out what's going on.
你们几个一起琢磨吧
You are gonna have to figure that out without me.
待会给我打电话也行 不过我得走了
You can call me later, but I gotta go.
祝你们玩的愉快
Hope you have fun.
珍妮特 回来 别走
Janet, come back. Don't leave.
不 劳丽 不 你们几个吓着我了
No, Lori. No. You guys are freaking me out.
这又怎么了? 她有点焦躁 不过很正常
What's with that? She went from uptight but normal...
焦躁到丧失理智了
...to uptight and totally insane.
你干吗要这样? 她亲眼看见别人死在她面前
Why do you gotta be a prick? She saw somebody die.
- 我们也是啊 - 是啊 我们也都吓坏了啊
- So did we. - Yeah, and we're all freaked out.
你能不能对"死"不要那么敏感吗?
Would it kill you to be sensitive?
我不知道
I don't know.
我以前从来没试过
I've never tried it.
你要去哪?
Where are you going?
如果你的推断没错的话
If you're right about this whole crash thing...
我要好好利用剩下的时间
then I'm going to make the most of every moment I have left.
我要尽我所能 好好享受了
I'm gonna go get laid.
如果所剩时日不多 我就要争分夺秒的活
If I'm dying, I'm trying.
我们要抗争到底 伙计们
Keep up the good fight, guys.
我要是碰到珍妮特 我会看看她情况怎么样的
And if I happen to bump into Janet, I will check on her.
谢了
Thanks.
这下好了
Well, that went well.
是啊 朋友们都觉得我们疯了 简直糟糕透了
Yeah, our friends think we're crazy. It's great.
或许我们还真的疯了呢
Well, maybe we are.
或许这仅仅是巧合罢了
Look, they're probably just some weird coincidences.
你这样认为?
You think?
我希望是巧合
I hope so.
尼克 你怎么看?
Nick? What did you see?
- 我觉得我们可以阻止这一切 - 怎么阻止?
- I think we can stop it. - How?
我们得去赛车场
We gotta go to the racetrack.
我的上帝啊
Oh, my God.
瞧瞧这地方
Look at this place.
这些人都…
All those people just...
- 我想离开这 - 我知道 我明白
- I don't wanna be here. - I know, I know.
但这是我唯一知道的如何帮助我
But this is the only thing that I can think of
回想起先后顺序的方法
to help me remember the order.
就在这 我们当时就在这
It's over here. This is where we were.
看看是否管用
Let's see if this works.
修理工的女朋友最先死
The mechanic's girlfriend dies first.
接着是那个种族歧视的人和他老婆
Then that racist and his wife.
接下来是那个带小孩的女人
That woman with the kids, she was next.
走吧 我们不该在这的 赶紧走吧
Let's go. We shouldn't be here. Let's go.
我都记不起来这些人都是什么时候死的了
I can't remember who dies when.
没事的
It's okay.
我好迷茫 不知道该怎么办了
I don't know what to do. I can't...
或者这不是个好办法
Maybe this was a really bad idea.
不是的
No.
我必须得试试
I gotta try.
你这样擅自闯入 最好给我个足够的理由
You better have a damn good reason for trespassing.
我需要回忆起顺序
I just need to remember the order.
听起来简直不可理喻
Young man, that sounds crazy.
可能这会对你有帮助
But maybe this will help you.
我们所有的录像资料都在这
Now, this will bring up all our video cameras right here.
这
There.
这就是那个修理工死去的地方
That's where that guy in the mechanic jacket dies.
这么说 他就是下个了
So he's next, then.
我想是的
I think so.
那里的崩塌又要了亨特和珍妮特的命
That collapse kills Hunt and Janet.
你就是这个时候死的
And that's when you die.
然后是劳丽
And then Lori.
然后是我
Then me.
如果我们能救下修理工
Maybe if we can stop this mechanic from...
我们就能改变这个顺序
getting killed, we can break the chain...
这样的话 我们这些人就安全了
and the rest of us will be safe.
究竟要怎么办呢? 我是说 我们甚至都不知道他叫什么
But how? I mean, we don't even know his name.
我们对他一无所知
We know nothing about him.
不过我们知道他在哪工作
But we do know where he works.
格兰斯特海关
Grandstate Customs.
必须要把传动齿轮装好
Gotta finish up that differential.
把这个焊在玻璃纤维上
Bond that to the fibreglass on it.
- 弄好了吗? - 快了 马上就好
- Done with that impact? - Yeah, hold on a second.
这里也需要焊接一下 对吗?
You just want that spot-welded, right?
嘿 过来搭把手
Hey, can you give me a hand with this test probe?
好东西
Good stuff, man.
- 嘿 - 你还好吧?
- Hey! - Are you okay?
这个傻子是谁?
Who's the fucking moron?
你 你在这干吗?
You. What are you doing here?
来找你
Trying to find you.
听我说 你现在有生命危险
Look, man, I'm sorry for being blunt,
死神会很快光顾你的
but your life's in danger. You're gonna die.
在事故发生前离开体育场的
Three of the people who left that...
那3个人现在都死了
stadium before that accident they're now dead.
真的很抱歉 我们推断 你就是下一个
I'm sorry, but we think that you're gonna be next.
你没开玩笑吧?
You're serious?
安迪
Andy.
不能让这些人在这呆着
You know you can't have these people here.
带他们出去 任何人不得入内
Take them outside. No visitors in here.
走吧
Let's go.
听我说 我正努力让生活重回正轨
Look, man, I'm trying to put my life back together, okay?
我是说 看着娜迪亚在我面前死去…
I mean, watching Nadia die like that in front of me...
我能理解你的感受
Hey, I know exactly how you feel.
在一次车祸中 我也痛失爱妻爱女
I lost my wife and my daughter in a car accident.
当时我开着车 醉酒驾车
I was driving and I was drunk.
以后的每天 我都谴责我自己
Every day, I ask myself how come...
为什么死的不是我
it couldn't be me instead of them.
此后很长一段时间 我都活在痛苦和愤怒中…
For a long time, I carried so much pain and anger...
但这样做无疑是在摧残她们留给我的回忆
it was actually destroying their memory.
所以现在我每天都为她们俩继续活着
So now I try to live each day in their name.
嘿 伙计们 我真不想第一个把这坏消息告诉你们
Hey, guys, I hate to break it to you,
不过我真的有种很不祥的预感
but I'm getting a really bad feeling.
听我说 孩子 我每天都围着这危险的仪器转
Look, kid, I'm around dangerous equipment every day.
如果我必死无疑 死神也不会等到现在才召见我
If I was meant to die, it would've happened by now.
当心
Look out!
- 我的天啊! - 你没事吧 安迪?
- Holy shit. - You okay, Andy?
没事 我没事
Yeah, I'm okay.
我猜 现在还没轮到我死
Well, I guess it's not my turn to die.
你们都要保重啊
Y'all take care.
上帝啊! 你没事吧?
Holy! You all right?
派20个人过来
Show us 20 at the body shop.
亲爱的 要是你能阻止下一个死亡的发生
Honey, I mean, if you can stop the next death...
我稍微有了些头绪 不过没办法把它们联系到一起
I'm seeing clues, but I can't piece them together.
- 你得好好想想 到底谁是下一个? - 我不知道
- You gotta think. Who's next? - I don't know.
我们必须得去警告你的朋友们
We have to warn your friends.
- 怎么警告? - 下一个是谁?
- How? - Well, which one is next?
崩塌的时候他们都死了 我也不知道
They both die in the collapse. I don't know.
尼克 好好想想 集中精力
Nick, think. Focus.
也许他们会死
One of them had to be first, even if it...
但肯定有先有后
was one second before the other one.
到底是亨特先还是珍妮特?
Was it Hunt, or was it Janet?
你得找到珍妮特
You gotta find Janet.
我去找亨特 好吧?
I'm gonna find Hunt. Okay?
快点 快点
Oh, God. Faster, go faster.
快点 快点 快点
Go faster, go faster. Pick it up, pick it up.
别懒了 快点 再快点
Don't be lazy. Faster, faster.
别动 别动了 哦
Stop moving, stop moving, stop moving. Move. Oh!
不 拜托 别停 我还没完呢 还没完呢
No, come on. Wake up. No, we're not done. I'm not done.
拜托了
Come on.
不 不
No, no.
你他妈的别跟我开玩笑了
Are you fucking kidding me?
我4分钟前就爽过了
I finished, like, four minutes ago.
- 你以前都没玩过"驴拳" - 混蛋
- Ever play "Donkey Punch"? - Dick.
打扰一下 能帮帮我这个深陷囵囫的艺术家吗?
Excuse me, miss, but could you help a struggling artist?
当然了
Sure.
- 谢了 - 祝你今天愉快
- Thanks. - Have a nice day.
看看这个好心人施舍了我们多少 布朗尼
Let's see what we got here, Browning.
1分钱? 真扯蛋!
A penny? That's some bullshit.
该死
Oh, damn it.
这下好了
Great.
快点 你个垃圾
Come on, you custom piece of shit.
快点 接电话啊 快点
Come on, pick up the phone. Come on.
你在哪呢? 快点
Aah. Where are you at? Come on.
我是亨特 你知道该干什么
This is Hunt. You know what to do.
亨特 听我说 伙计
Hunt, listen to me, buddy, listen.
不要靠近水 听见没?
No water, okay? Stay away from water.
您有三条紧急信息
You have three messages marked urgent.
真搞笑 是吧?
That's funny, huh?
- 把水枪给我 - 不
- Give me the gun. - No, ha, ha.
快把水枪给我
Give me the fucking gun.
不
No.
我手机怎么了?
Fucked up my phone.
该死
Shit.
太好了
Perfect.
嘿 劳丽 我在洗车厂 5分钟后回你电话
Hey, Lori, I'm at the car wash. I'll call you back.
珍妮特 等等
Janet, wait. Wait. Shit.
知道这附近哪有洗车场吗?
Do you know if there's a car wash around here?
有啊 第18大街上就有
Yeah, there's one on 18th.
我们得去那
We gotta go there.
我应该的
Yes. I own you, machine.
劳丽?
Lori?
- 什么事这么重要? - 不要靠近水
- What's so important? - Don't go near water.
什么? 水?
What? Water?
- 不要靠近水! - 什么水? 劳丽?
- Don't go near water! - Water? Lori?
等等 劳丽?
Wait. Lori?
该死
Shit.
无信号
No service.
该死
Shit.
快点 快点
Come on, come on, come on.
快点
Come on.
天啊 不
Lord, no.
关上啊
Close!
停下 我的天啊 不要
Oh, stop it! Oh, my God, no!
哦 天啊 救命啊
Oh, God! Help me!
来人啊! 救命啊!
Please! Somebody, please!
接电话 珍妮特
Pick up the phone, Janet.
救命啊
Oh, God! Help!
我的天啊 上帝啊!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
快到了
We're almost there.
糟了!
Oh, shit. Fore!
不 不
No, no, no.
- 就在这 - 快点
- There it is. - Hurry.
从后面绕过去 乔治 她在那里
Go around back, George. She's in there.
不!
No!
快走 快!
Go, go, go!
劳丽 劳丽 快救我出去
Lori! Lori, get me out of here!
我来了 坚持住!
Shit. I'm coming. Just hold on.
快点 快救她出来
Come on, get her out.
- 劳丽 救我 - 我已经很尽力了
- Lori, help me! - I'm trying!
来 到这来 我抓住你了
Come here, I got you. I got you.
亨特
Hunt.
- 你有保险吗? - 有啊
- So do you have insurance? - Yeah.
我们现在该怎么办?
What are we supposed to do now?
我是说 我们俩会有什么不测吗?
I mean, what's gonna happen to us?
救下珍妮特要么能毁了死神的名单
You know, saving Janet either destroyed death's list...
我们全部能安全回家
and all of us are home free,
要么就是跳过她…
or it skips her for now and then...
这么说 我就是下一个了
And I'm next.
乔治 你不能放弃
George, you can't give up.
不会 没事的
No, it's okay.
"没事"是什么意思?
What do you mean, "it's okay"?
我是说 只要我们齐心协力…
I mean, maybe if we all stick together...
不 这对我来说倒没什么
No, I'm at peace with it.
我的家人都在等我
And, um, my family's waiting for me.
我准备好了
I'm ready to go.
我们的事情做完后
When we're done in here, we need to
我们得保证安全到达卧室
make sure to safe-proof the bedroom next.
我真不知道乔治怎么这么镇定
I don't understand how George can be so calm about things.
或许他吓坏了吧
Maybe he was in shock.
不 不是这样的
No, that's not it.
他思维很清晰
It was very clear. It's...
我感觉他已经接受了
It's like he just accepted it.
我以为他已经放弃了
I think he's given up.
他要是有什么不测的话 我就是下一个
If he dies, I'm next.
如果真是这样的话
And when that happens,
你们就应该离的远点
maybe you should just keep your distance.
宝贝 你说什么胡话呢
Babe, what are you talking about? Come on.
我不想你们任何人有任何闪失
I don't want anything to happen to you.
如果我们在一起的话
And if we're together, it makes it easier
死神更容易一下子带走我们俩
for death to take both of us.
我才不管会发生什么呢 我们生死与共
I don't care what happens. We are in this together.
听我说
Look.
或许不必要再有人死了
Maybe no one else has to die.
我们得去告诉乔治
We should go tell George.
有人吗?
Hello?
乔治
George.
我们推断救出珍妮特就能破坏这个顺序
We think saving Janet broke the chain.
乔治?
George?
- 乔治? - 乔治?
- George? - George?
我的天啊 乔治…
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. No. George...
我的天 你疯了吗?
Oh, my God. Are you crazy?
我们一起经历了这么多
After everything that we've been through.
你干吗要自杀?
Why are you trying to kill yourself?
顺天意而已
Trying to give God what I thought he wanted.
我已经想了一整天要自杀了
I've been trying to kill myself all day.
喝了一整瓶的安眠药 刚才吐了出来
Took a bottle of painkillers. I just threw them up.
然后我去了车库
Then I went to the garage,
钩住了排气的软管
hooked a hose from the tailpipe...
却又卡在车下了 车子不停的熄火
stuck it inside the car, the car kept stalling.
然后…
Then...
那就等等吧
So wait.
救下珍妮特一定是打乱了顺序
Saving Janet must have destroyed the list, then.
我们得好好庆祝了
I think congratulations are in order.
敬我们打破了死神的顺序
To breaking the chain.
- 要苹果酒吗? - 谢谢
- Apple cider? - Thank you.
- 谢天谢地 - 举杯庆祝吧
- Thank God. - And a toast.
- 敬我们还活着 - 还活着
- To life. - To life.
我们有了第二次机会
We've been given a second chance.
你有什么打算?
So, what are you guys gonna do with it?
我有一大堆的打算
I have a few plans for us, ha, ha.
旅游 去巴黎或者海边看看
Lots of travelling, like Paris, maybe some beaches, St-Tropez.
我很感激我们还有
I'm just thankful we have our...
大把大把的时间可以活
whole lives ahead of us, you know?
是啊
Yeah.
现在一切都结束了
Now this is over,
我不会再把每天的新生活当作理所当然的了
I'm not gonna take another day for granted.
再也不会了
Ever.
或许我们不该再空口谈论了
You know, maybe it's time to stop talking
应该都付诸实践
about doing stuff and actually start doing it.
生命只有一次 对吧?
You only live once, right?
我就是这个意思
That's what I'm talking about.
我去拿点甜点来
Let me get the cookies.
我们成功了
We made it.
的确是
We did.
- 嘿 - 嘿 宝贝
- Hey. - Hey, babe.
你去旅行社预约了吗?
Did you get the traveller's checks?
是的
Yes, I did.
需要我去超市带点什么吗?
Need anything from the mall?
不用了 不缺什么
No, I think we're good.
你确定真不去看电影?
You sure you don't wanna come to the movie?
- 是个3D动画 - "爱情在逝去"?
- It's in 3-D. - Love Lays Dying?
不了 我不去了 听起来像是女生剧场
Yeah, I think I'll be all right. Sounds like a chickflick.
不过 你回家的时候 我会把行李都收拾妥当的
But, uh, I'll have everything packed by the time you get home.
阿姆斯特丹 我们来了
Amsterdam, here we come.
真不敢相信我们真的来了
I can't believe we're actually going.
你知道嘛 珍妮特都快嫉妒疯了
You know, Janet is so incredibly jealous.
说到这了 她快醒了 我得走了
Speaking of, she's walking up right now. I'm gonna run, okay?
- 替我问候她 - 我会的
- Tell her I said hi. - I will.
- 我爱你 - 我也爱你 早点回来
- Love you. - Love you too. Be home soon.
- 拜拜 - 拜拜
- Bye. - Bye.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi, ha, ha.
约翰 高速车祸不为人知的幸存者
John Doe, the unknown survivor of the speedway crash...
目前身份已得到证实 已经通知其家属
has finally been named now that his family's been notified.
乔纳森在废墟中被解救了出来
Jonathan Groves was rescued in the rubble.
乔治 你什么时候来医院?
George, how fast can you meet me at the hospital?
听我说 我们把顺序弄错了
Look, man, we got the order wrong.
记得坐我前面的那个人吗? 那个牛仔?
Remember that guy who sat in front of me? The cowboy?
他没死 也就是说 他是下一个
He didn't die, which means he's next.
5分钟内赶紧到那 我就在路上了
Look, just be there in five. I'm on my way.
你感觉好点了吗?
You feeling okay, Mr. Suby?
你为什么这么关心?
Ha. Why do you care?
你知道你的同胞在朝鲜战争中阵亡了多少吗?
You know how many of your kind I killed in Korea?
- 我是中国人 先生 - 都一样
- I'm Chinese, sir. - Ha, same difference.
你得赶紧到PT3来一趟
I need you in PT 3 right now.
- 好的 - 我是说现在
- Okay. - And I do mean now.
- 好的 - 谢谢你
- Okay. - Thank you.
很快回来伺候你洗澡
Be back in a few minutes to get you into that tub.
哈福利医生到妇产科来一趟
Dr. Helfrich to Obstetrics.
嘿 有人吗? 救命啊
Hey. Somebody. Hey. Help.
忘了把水龙头关掉了
Forgot to turn the water off.
救命啊
Help.
救命 救命啊!
Help. Somebody help.
- 菲恩医生2861分机呼叫 - 救命啊
- Dr. Finn, extension 2861. - Somebody help.
菲恩医生 2861分机呼叫
Dr. Finn, extension 2861.
乔治 乔治
George. George.
劳丽哪去了?
Where's Lori?
我整个下午都在打电话发短信
I've been calling and texting all afternoon.
可她就是没有回音
She's not picking up.
或许没什么事呢 来吧
Maybe it won't matter. Come on.
名单上怎么还会有别的人呢?
How can there be someone else on the list?
他没有跟我们一起离开赛车场啊
He didn't leave the racetrack with us.
如果我当初像预感里预示的让他离开
If I would've asked him to move
他肯定不会死
like in the premonition, he would've died.
他活了下来 所以你没法自杀
He survived. That's why you couldn't kill yourself.
你不是下一个 他才是 完全跟命运无关
You weren't next, he was. It wasn't destined at all.
也就是说 如果他死了 我就是下一个了
So if he dies, I'm next again.
太好了
Great, man.
- 打扰 - 泰勒医生到病理科室来一趟
- Excuse me.- Dr. Taylor to Pathology.
泰勒医生到病理科室来一趟
Dr. Sheila Taylor to Pathology.
耶
Yeah.
真就是时尚
Those are really hot.
是啊 我超爱 我喜欢…
Yes. I love these. I like how they...
- 哦 - 啊 怎么了?
- Oh! - Aah! What the hell?
哦
Ow!
嘿 停下
Ugh, hey. Stop...
真是蠢蛋 弄不好要出人命的
That's genius. Someone could get killed.
伙计 我有预感
Man, I'm feeling something.
别失去信心
Don't lose hope, man.
我们要是留意周围的危险的话
If we keep an eye out for signs of danger,
我想应该没问题
I think we got a shot.
我们要赶紧找到劳丽和珍妮特
Let's just go find Lori and Janet.
不 不 我是说 像幻觉记忆一样
No, no, not that. I mean, it's like dej?vu.
我妻子说 幻觉记忆就像是以上帝的方式来…
My wife said that dej?vu is like God's way of...
- 我的天啊 快点 快走 - 好的
- Oh, my goodness. Hurry, let's go. - Okay.
- 谢谢你 - 好的 谢了
- Oh, thank you very much. - Okay, thanks.
嗨 这东西有六个包装的吗?
Hi. Do you have these in a six?
有 我们的货每天都换新鲜的
Yes, we bring them in fresh every day.
- 你好 - 哦
- Hello. - Oh!
- 好了 我们走吧 - 你觉得怎么样?
- Cool, let's go. - What do you think?
啊
Ah...
很可爱 还很合脚
Well, they're cute yet functional.
我喜欢
I like them.
人们常说:"虽然我现在年纪大了"
They say, "I'm getting older,
"不过照样喜欢派对"
but I still like to party." Ha, ha.
不是为你买的 是为尼克买的
Ha, ha, I didn't buy them for you, I bought them for Nick.
他喜欢我穿运动鞋
He likes me in sneaks.
是啊 你得抓紧
Yeah, just get a 2-by-48.
就在角落的支柱旁
Right off the corner brace?
查看下尺寸 不是很合适
Check the measurement. It's not fitting.
窗户那边过不去
Those windows won't pass.
没错 尺寸为90
Yeah, 90 on that.
恩 看起来不错
Yeah, that looks fine.
赶紧钉上 已经是水平位置了
Go ahead and nail it off, it's level.
嗯 就在拐角处
Yeah, around the corner.
- 午饭时间 - 好的
- Lunch, boys. - Okay.
1小时后回来
Back in an hour.
那个卖酸奶的店还在营业吗?
Is that yoghurt place still open?
应该还在营业
Yeah, I think they're still here.
等等 我鞋带卡住了
Wait. My shoelace is caught.
- 什么? - 我鞋带卡住了
- What? - My shoelace is stuck.
- 哦 拿着 - 帮我把鞋带弄出来
- Oh, okay, here. - Just help me get it out.
我来把…
Look, I'm gonna grab your...
还是没弄出来 珍妮特
It's not coming out, though, Janet.
- 别害怕 - 用力拉我的腿
- Don't freak out. - Pull my leg harder.
帮我弄出来 松都没松一下
Help me try to get it out. It's not coming loose.
- 我正在努力 - 缠到我脚踝上去了
- I am trying. I'm pulling. - It's twisting my ankle.
该死的
Fuck.
我早该注意到的
I should've seen that one coming.
- 你没事吧? - 我没事
- Are you okay? - Yeah, I'm okay.
这是两张爱情在逝去的电影票 祝您玩的开心
Here's two for Love Lays Dying. Enjoy the show.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 女士们 你们好 - 你好
- Hi, ladies. - Hello.
- 13剧院在左手边第二个入口 - 谢谢
- Theatre 13, second door on your left. - Thanks.
- 你想要点什么? - 不知道
- So, what do you want? - I don't know.
你要去哪啊?
Where the hell you going?
快走 甩掉他
Go. Go now. Cut him off.
- 你疯了? - 它就在前面
- Are you fucking nuts? - It's just up ahead.
等等 我们很快就到
Hold on, pumpkin. We'll be there in no time.
真是太酷了
That's really cool.
- 前面的低点 混蛋 - 真是荒谬
- Down in front, asshole. - That's so ridiculous.
先生 挪一下
sir, move your feet.
把这塞耳朵里 待会会很吵的
Put these in your ears. It's gonna get loud.
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
别生我气
Look, don't get mad at me...
你记得尼克说过 他能预感事情吗?
but do you remember when Nick said that he could see signs...
能预感一些不祥的事情发生?
before something bad was gonna happen?
我觉得我现在正有这些预感
Well, now I think I'm seeing them.
劳丽 结束了 不会有不好的事情发生的
Lori, it's over. Nothing is gonna happen.
- 我们能不能专心看电影? - 我走了
- Now can we please watch the movie? - I'm going.
你开玩笑吧?
Are you kidding me?
- 所有人都离开 - 我们没法办到的
- Everybody off. - We'll never make it.
就快爆炸了
It's gonna blow.
劳丽 劳丽
Lori. Lori.
- 劳丽 - 闭嘴 老兄
- Lori! - Shut up, man.
再见了 混蛋
Bye-bye, suckers.
迪克斯
"Dixieland."
- 有事情不对劲 - 开玩笑吧
- Something's wrong. - No kidding.
坐我旁边的人一直叽歪个不停
The person next to me won't shut up.
不 我是认真的 很不对劲
No, I'm serious. Something's wrong.
就像我们当初在赛车场一样
Things are happening just like at the track.
- 劳丽 你们在这里啊 - 尼克
- Lori, you in here? - Nick.
- 一切还没结束 - 什么?
- It's not over. - What?
乔治死了
George is dead.
珍妮特 快点 我们得赶紧离开这
Janet, come on. We have to leave right now.
不 不 我不要再这样了 你们俩都疯了
No. No, I can't keep doing this, okay? You're both nuts.
珍妮特 我们得走了 快点
Janet, we gotta go. Come on.
不 难道你没看见吗?
No. Don't you see?
这才是我本该呆的地方
This is where I was supposed to be...
而不是去看比赛
in the first place, not that race.
- 快点 - 我本该来看这场电影
- Come on. Come on. - I was meant to see this movie.
再见 混蛋
Bye-bye, suckers.
珍妮特
Janet!
劳丽 快点
Lori, come on!
找到出口 不要慌张
Find the way to the exit. Remain calm.
一切都会好的
Everything's gonna be okay.
快走 快走
Let's go! Let's go!
- 我抓住你了 - 拉我上来!
- I got you. - Pull me up!
尼克
Nick! Nick!
- 救我 救命啊 - 坚持住
- Help me! Help me! - Hold on! Hold on!
- 沿着我胳膊爬! - 别松手!
- Climb up my arm! - Don't let me go!
沿着我胳膊往上爬
Climb up my arm!
别 坚持住 我抓住你了
No! Hold on, I got you. I got you.
不 不
No, no, no!
劳丽 不 劳丽
Lori, no! Lori, no!
我是说 这就是幻觉记忆
I mean, it's dej?vu.
我妻子说 幻觉记忆是上帝…
My wife said that dej?vu is God's way...
当心!
Look out!
- 快! - 快求援!
- Hurry. - Get some help!
- 救命啊 - 这边
- Help. - Over here!
劳丽
Lori.
嘿 当心点
Hey, watch it.
前面的低点 混蛋
Down in front, asshole.
嘿 快点 伙计
Hey, come on, man.
- 当心 - 嘿
- Watch out. - Hey.
嘿 快点
Hey, come on.
珍妮特 有些不对劲
Janet, something's wrong.
快点 拜托了
Come on, come on, come on.
见鬼
Uh, damn it.
该死的
Fuck! Oh!
我们把顺序弄错了
We were wrong about the order.
如果顺序错了 后果如何?
What if we're wrong about the chain?
后果是我们根本就不会来到这
Then we wouldn't be here at all.
但我却来了 要在这看场电影
And yet here I am, trying to watch a movie...
坐在我身边的死党却要死要活的
despite my best friend going crazy next to me.
哦 不要
Oh, fuck.
该死
Oh, shit. Shit.
这里要爆炸了 快走
It's gonna blow. Move it!
快点
Come on. Come on.
再见 混蛋
Bye-bye, suckers.
我猜 这就是我给世人留下的影像了
I guess this is how I'm gonna be remembered.
谢谢
Thanks.
试着系在这里
Try to tie it off right there.
很好
That's good.
就在城市这边
Just this side of the Union City.
嘿 伙计 打扰一下
Hey, man, excuse me.
这东西是不是该在这边?
Is this thing supposed to be this way?
难道不应该绑在一起吗?
Isn't it supposed to be screwed tighter?
没错
You're right.
好的 待会就找人弄好
Tell you what, we'll get somebody on that.
要想安全 必须得付出 相信我
Pays to be safe, man. Trust me.
弄下来
That's one down.
你现在就想见他们吗?
You wanna meet up with them now?
- 一小杯薄荷茶 - 谢了
- Small mint tea. - Thanks.
- 她要一小杯拿铁咖啡 - 谢了
- Small latte for you. - Thank you.
我要…
And for me...
这是什么鬼东西?
Um, what the hell is that?
一个巨型的奶油巧克力
A giant chococcino with whipped cream,
巧克力糖浆
chocolate syrup, caramel and sprinkles.
看起来真恶心
That looks disgusting.
看的我都恶心死了
Yeah. I'm going into a diabetic coma just looking at it.
那我可没话说了 以前不是这样的
Well, what can I say, ladies? It looked good.
喝起来真是难以下咽
Yeah, but it tastes totally disgusting.
你们就是救火英雄吧?
Say, you're the guy who stopped that mall fire, aren't you?
可真是救了不少人啊
You saved a lot of lives, man.
我只是碰巧在那个时间出现在那个地点而已
I was just at the right place at the right time.
有时候 就是得有这个运气才能"碰巧"上
Mm-hm. Sometimes that's all it takes.
好吧 的确很奇怪
Okay, that was really weird.
嘿 别搅了我的兴致
Hey, don't knock my fan base.
我很喜欢你的包包
I love your bag, by the way.
- 哦 谢了 我刚买的 - 是吗? 在哪买的?
- Oh, thanks. I actually just got it. - Did you? Where?
是啊 就在布维格旁边 新开的店
Yeah. There's a place right next to Brevig's. It just opened.
- 布维格? - 是啊 就在购物中心
- Brevig's? - Yeah, it's in that shopping center.
有个杂货店 还有个…
There's a grocery store and a card shop'and then there's a...
- 看起来就像是个饰品店 - 哦 明白了
- It's like a little accessories store. - Oh, yeah.
超级可爱的 你要是想买…
It's super cute. If you want one...
这种包的话 他们只有2个
of these purses, they have it in plaid.
- 哈哈 这就是另一个吧? - 是啊
- Ha, ha, is that the only other one? - Yeah.
他们就制造了2个?
They only made two?
你觉得呢 宝贝?
What do you think, babe?
嘿 太空人醒醒 你回到地球了吗?
Hey, uh, space cadet, you wanna come back down to Earth?
如果我们什么都没改变 会是怎么个结局呢?
What if we didn't change anything?
你说什么呢?
What are you talking about?
你要干什么?
Whoa, whoa, what are you doing?
如果我们现在身处此地
What if us being here right now...
就是一开始就安排好了的呢?
...was the plan from the beginning?